https://www.rolfebenson.com/privacy-policy/

Hit enter to search or ESC to close
Privacy PolicyInformation is the cornerstone of our ability to meet and exceed our clients’ expectations. At Rolfe, Benson LLP we are committed to maintaining the security, confidentiality and accuracy of the personal information we collect, to provide the highest level of service to our clients. Your trust is the foundation of our business, and with that in mind, we have developed a comprehensive Privacy Policy for handling personally identifying information. As Chartered Professional Accountants, we are governed by the Rules of Professional Conduct which have always, and will continue to, guarantee privacy and confidentiality of your personal information.    What Does the Privacy Policy Cover?Our Privacy Policy covers Rolfe, Benson LLP’s treatment of your personally identifying information when you use our services or visit our Website. This policy also covers Rolfe, Benson LLP’s handling of any personally identifying information with our business partners, which may include any national or international affiliation.    What is Personally Identifying Information Collected for?We collect and use personal information generally to provide services for our clients for the following purposes:To assist us in providing services pertaining to the preparation of your financial statements.For the preparation of your taxation and other information returns as required by various governmental and other regulatory authorities.To provide advice to you on personal financial planning, business and estate planning, valuation and other business and personal advisory services.To better understand your needs and to determine the suitability of other services we may be able to offer to you. ConsentWe will not collect, use or disclose your personally identifying information without your consent. By providing us with your personal information for the purposes listed above, you consent to our collection and use of the information for those purposes. With respect to personal information that you provide for the purpose of preparation of taxation and other returns, you consent to the transmission of such personal information to the appropriate governmental and regulatory authorities.You have the right to refuse or withdraw your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. In such cases, refusal or withdrawal may prohibit or adversely affect the completion of our professional engagement. We will advise you if this becomes the case.    Information Sharing and DisclosureRolfe, Benson LLP may only send personally identifying information about you to other organizations when we have your consent to share this information. We may disclose personal information without your consent when required by law, but the information we provide will be limited to only what is legally required.    Retention, Accuracy and SafeguardingTo serve you better and to preserve the information for governmental and professional purposes, we will retain and safeguard your information for as long as we determine is necessary (even if you are no longer a client).We will continue to use appropriate technologies to maintain high security standards to ensure the protection of your information. While we use up to date technology to protect your personal information when it is transmitted electronically, please be aware that no electronic transmission can be guaranteed to be completely secure.In the course of delivering our services to you, we understand that you may disclose to us personal information that you have collected regarding your employees, customers and other parties. You have our assurance and commitment that this information will be kept private and confidential and will not be released to any third party (other than as may be required by law), unless we obtain your consent.You may, upon written request, review your personal information and request corrections, if necessary. We are committed to maintaining accurate information and urge you to notify us promptly of any changes in your personal information.    Collecting Non-Personally Identifying Information (IP Addresses and Cookies)You can visit our Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself (including your email address). Our Web server may collect the IP address and domain you used to access our Web site, the type and version of web browser and operating system you are using, the number, duration and frequency of visits to our Web site and the Web site you came from and visit next.This anonymous information cannot be traced to a specific individual user. It is used by Rolfe, Benson LLP to measure the number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed, most popular preferences and other statistics about Web site visitors. This information allows us to determine the characteristics of users on Rolfe, Benson LLP’s Web site and our most popular services. Rolfe, Benson LLP may use this data to monitor Web site performance for systems administration purposes, or to make our Web site easier and more convenient to use, as well as improving our services and tracking visitor information (eg. the number of visitors to our Web site).    E-mailAll emails from Rolfe, Benson LLP (including any attachments) may contain confidential or privileged information and is intended for the sole use of the person(s) to whom it is addressed. If you are not the intended recipient, please notify the sender immediately, and delete all copies. Any unauthorized review, use, alteration, disclosure of this e–mail by an unintended recipient is prohibited. Any advice contained herein should be treated as preliminary advice only and subject to formal written confirmation. We are not responsible for updating our advice for changes in law or interpretation after the date hereof.    Our Commitment to YouEvery one of our partners, employees and contractors is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of all personal information to which they have access. Our employees are trained to know and respect our privacy policy, and compliance with our policies and procedures for protecting personal information is a condition of their employment.    Contacting UsIf you have any questions about our privacy policies, please contact our Privacy Officer:Privacy Officer Rolfe, Benson LLP Chartered Professional Accountants 1500 – 1090 West Georgia Street Vancouver BC V6E 3V7 604-684-1101 email: privacy@rolfebenson.com    RecourseIf you have not received a satisfactory response to your privacy concerns after contacting our Privacy Officer, you may direct your question or complaint to the following:Chartered Professional Accountants British Columbia – www.bccpa.caChartered Professional Accountants Canada –www.cpacanada.caOffice of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada – www.privcom.ca Changes to our Privacy PolicyRolfe, Benson LLP reserves the right to amend this privacy policy from time to time. 1500-1090 West Georgia Street Vancouver, BC V6E 3V7 Tel: (604) 684-1101 Fax: (604) 684-7937 admin@rolfebenson.com Get AroundHomeAbout UsExpertiseClient CentreCareersContact Us Service AreasTax Planning & ComplianceAccounting & AssuranceEstate PlanningManagement Advisory ServicesNon-ResidentsCharities & Not-for Profits IndustriesRetail & HospitalityReal Estate & ConstructionManufacturing, Wholesale & DistributionNPOs, Foundations & CharitiesProfessional ServicesTechnology 2020 @ Rolfe, Benson LLP Chartered Professional Accountants
Privacy Policy | Terms
HomeAbout UsExpertiseIndustriesRetail & HospitalityReal Estate & ConstructionManufacturing, Wholesale & DistributionNot-for-Profit Organizations, Foundations & CharitiesProfessional ServicesTechnologyServicesTax Planning & ComplianceAccounting & AssuranceEstate PlanningManagement Advisory ServicesNon-ResidentsCharities & Not-for ProfitsCareersTeamClient CentreAccounting FormsPay An InvoiceClient Portal & File TransferUseful LinksContact Us1500-1090 West Georgia Street Vancouver, BC V6E 3V7 Tel: (604) 684-1101 Fax: : (604) 684-7937 admin@rolfebenson.com
